are also going
to cut delivery
cut delivery
costs dramatically.
Did you know
there are already
are already
four million
deliveries per
year by drones?
Now, to be
by drones?
sure, Zipline, one
sure, Zipline,
of the companies
in our venture
fund, is responsible
our venture
for, I think,
half of those.
I think,
But we
believe that
the cost to
deliver by drone
deliver by
will cut delivery
costs, right now,
cut delivery
DoorDash, $15 per,
DoorDash, $15
to less than
a dollar, so
a 90% reduction
90% reduction
over time.
So this is
another huge market
another huge
percolating out there.
percolating out
And we're so
excited because
we believe
we're now in
we're now
the prime time
for the reason
prime time
I founded Ark.
I founded Ark
founded Ark.
in 2014 for
in 2014
this reason.